I think that like it's important for the
public to see what we do as a day-to-day
basis and what's urgent what's not
urgent as an emergency physician there's
very few things that are truly
emergencies but at the same time it's
the worst day of someone else's life so
it's always nice to be a friendly face
when you can be and to be there to
receive people when they need us I'm
pretty sure that people might not have
picked me out as the doctor in the scene
so I think it's important as a woman to
stand up and say as a woman of my
background that I am a doctor too
there's always memorable patients that
really pass by a guy who came in was in
the weight room for a number of hours
and then got really really sick and that
day we were able to save his life
because his aorta had burst open and
actually you know like we diagnosed it
within a couple of minutes of him having
a drop of his blood pressure not looking
great but we actually had to do some
chest compressions on him to get to the
o.r and it was a fairly dramatic save so
thanks to all the docs and nurses that
were involved in the surgeon who took
him to the or and saved his life but two
days later he was excavated from the I
and the ICU and he was transferred to
the ward before I go visit him and so it
was pretty amazing story what I hope
people can imagine is this scene that we
just shot but that when they're waiting
for six hours in the waiting room and or
the rapid assessment zone waiting to see
a doc that this is playing in the
background that someone else might be
having a worse day than them and I know
that's hard when your issue is like your
most important issue and you were there
yourself but but I think it's about
creating that shared consciousness that
we see the sickest patients first and
the people that have just been in a big
accident or something like that we're
going to take care of them as best we
can first and then we're going to move
towards patients that
I need more time